find a comfortable position close your eyes and enter your level
by yourself using the three -to -one method followed by a ten
-to -one countdown I will then come in after that with with
some positive statements and affirmations.
Take your time.
Thank you.
relax take a deep breath and as you exhale relax and go
deeper you will continue to listen to my voice you will continue
to follow the instructions at this level of the mind or any
other level including the outer conscious level
this is for your benefit you desire it and it is so
the difference between genius mentality and lay mentality
is that geniuses use more of their minds and use them in
a special manner
You are now learning to use more of your mind and to
use it in a special manner.
The following are beneficial statements that you may
occasionally repeat while at these levels of the mind.
Repeat mentally after me.
My increasing mental faculties or for serving humanity better
every day in every way I am getting better better and better
I love and approve of myself
everything is coming together for good in my life
I am a radiant being filled with light and love
I will always maintain a perfectly healthy body, mind, and
immune system.
Now, at this time, you will begin the process of forgiving
yourself and allowing increased peace and harmony feel how
deeply comfortable you are now focus on your mental screen that
is past your eyelids and a little higher than the horizontal
level of sight keep in mind that forgiveness brings forth peace
love joy and physical healing and we forgive by understanding
that we make mistakes and then releasing them forgiveness is
referred to as a surprise healer project an image of yourself on
your mental screen of a time in your life that needs to
be healed needs to be forgiven a time when you made a
mistake or made a wrong choice or what you felt was a
wrong choice allow that scene to start playing out in your
mind's eye let it play out
let it come now your mind protects you so let it play
your mind won't let you bring out more than you can handle
let that image that memory play out now how do you feel
as you experience this picture
feelings are a beautiful process of healing let them go if you
release tears that's a cleansing process it's okay embrace those
feelings
and now stop the picture where it is and for a moment
look at the younger you and keep in mind that whatever you
are now releasing and forgiving remember that while you may want
that to be different that was the best that you knew how
to do at the time now today
you may make a different choice but at that time that's what
you knew how to do with a great amount of compassion now
step into this picture the way you are now and go over
to the younger you and give yourself a big hug hold yourself
and say say I love you I forgive you I embrace you
I hold you you are beloved in whom I am well pleased
I love you I forgive you I embrace you I hold you
you are beloved in whom I am well -pleased
now for a moment feel yourself as the younger person feel the
embrace the the acceptance, the understanding, this is the
truth,
this is healing, feel that now,
feel that peace
when you are ready the current you can find yourself back in
the chair looking at the the younger you know that this
forgiveness is occurring and once again say to the younger you I
love you I forgive you let all parts of you forgive yourself
for any errors or mistakes that have occurred and say to
yourself mentally I love and forgive myself for any errors or
mistakes that have occurred I look at myself with love and
compassion I let go I forgive I I choose peace and joy,
love and compassion.
Once again, say to yourself mentally, I love and forgive myself
for any errors or mistakes that have occurred.
I look at myself with love and compassion I let go I
forgive I choose peace and joy joy love and compassion and when
you are ready allow the scene of the younger you that is
on your mental screen to begin to move away from you farther
and farther away so that it's becoming a little black dot off
in the distance and now imagine a big beautiful golden Sun
coming up over the horizon you've seen it before a hundred times
it nourishes the earth provides us with warmth and love peace
and growth allow that little black dot to fade into the Sun
now so that it's gone completely gone and now all previous
feelings are replaced with love compassion peace and healing and
this is so now take a deep breath and as you exhale
relax
as you heal all life is healing and now this time look
at your mental screen and this time work on forgiving a person
a situation or an organization that you need or want to forgive
keep in mind that other people make the best decisions they know
how to do also and that our job is to release these
negative feelings so that we are free and whole and joyful allow
a scene to come up on your screen any scene you choose
of a person and event or a situation that you now know
it's time to forgive and let go allow this scene to start
playing out let it play
How do you feel as you experience this picture?
Feelings are a beautiful process of healing.
Let them go.
If you release tears, that's a cleansing process.
It's okay.
Embrace those feelings.
now step into the picture and go over to the person situation
or organization and sit with them and take some time to express
your feelings let them know how you feel it's okay go ahead
head release your thoughts and your feelings and let them go
during this this time, you may also ask for forgiveness from
this person, situation,
or organization.
When you have finished that process, imagine yourself in your
chair and look at this person, situation or organization and
with everything you know about compassion and forgiveness look
at them and say I love you and forgive you I release
pain and suffering I choose peace
please forgive me in any way if I have hurt you all
is well all is peaceful
once again I love you and forgive you I release pain and
suffering I choose peace
please forgive me in any way if I have hurt you all
is well all is peaceful and when you are ready allow the
scene to begin to move away from you farther and farther away
from you so that it's becoming a little black dot way off
the distance now imagine a big beautiful golden Sun coming up
over the horizon you've seen it before a hundred times it
nourishes the earth provides us with warmth love peace and
growth
allow that little black dot to fade into the sun now so
that it's gone
and all previous feelings are now completely replaced with love
compassion peace and healing and this is so you are a beloved
being feel appreciation for choosing peace
now take a deep breath and as you exhale relax
every time you function at these levels of the mind you will
receive beneficial effects physically and mentally
you may use these levels of the mind to help yourself
to help your loved ones
or to help any human being who needs help physically and
mentally
you will always use these levels of the mind in a constructive
creative manner for all that is good honest and positive and
this is so you will continue to take part in constructive and
creative activities to make this a better world to live in so
that when we move on we shall have left behind a better
world for those who follow you will consider the whole of
humanity depending on their ages as fathers or mothers brothers
or sisters sons or daughters you You are a superior human being.
You have greater understanding, compassion, and patience with
others.
In a moment, I'm going to count from one to five and
cause a sound with my fingers. At that moment, you will open
your eyes, be wide awake, feeling fine and in perfect health,
feeling better than before one two coming out slowly now three
at the count of five you will open your eyes be wide
awake feeling fine and in perfect health feeling better than
before feeling Feeling the way you feel when you have slept the
right amount of revitalizing, refreshing, relaxing, healthy
sleep.
4, 5, eyes open, wide awake, feeling fine and healthy, feeling
better than before.